<archimate:ApplicationComponent
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="EudraCT"
    id="c74b534e-c7fb-44f2-a2fb-993b747c3e84"
    documentation="Det er kun SLV som har skrivetilgang til EudraCT i Norge.&#xA;&#xA;EudraCT is a database of all clinical trials which commenced in the Community from 1 May 2004, and also includes clinical trials linked to European paediatric drug development.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The following tasks can be performed from this page:&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Create a EudraCT number&#xD;&#xA;* Before any functionality of EudraCT can be used for a given clinical trial, a EudraCT number must be created in order to provide a unique reference for that trial.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Protocol-related information&#xD;&#xA;Sponsors can:&#xD;&#xA;* Create, save XML/PDF files of clinical trial applications locally.&#xD;&#xA;* Load locally saved clinical trial applications to complete, validate, compare, or to prepare a package for submission to a National Competent Authority.&#xD;&#xA;Third country data providers can:&#xD;&#xA;* Create, save XML/PDF files of third country files locally.&#xD;&#xA;* Create and post third country files to the EudraCT database.&#xD;&#xA;* Load locally saved third country files to complete, validate or post to the EudraCT database. To post third country files you will need to be registered as a third country data provider and log in. Contact: paediatrics@ema.europa.eu&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Result-related information&#xD;&#xA;To use result related functionality you will need to be registered as a results user, and log in.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Results users can:&#xD;&#xA;* Create, update, validate and post result data sets, and load summary attachments to the EudraCT database.&#xD;&#xA;* Save locally XML/PDF files of result data sets.&#xD;&#xA;* Load locally saved result data sets to update, validate, or to post to the EudraCT database.">
  <properties
      key="difi:namespace"
      value="legemiddelverket"/>
</archimate:ApplicationComponent>
